# **Lyboth Victorien Ntsana**

43 Kirkham Street London, SE18 2JS

Tel: 07852177515

Email: Lybothv@yahoo.com www.linkedin.com/in/lyboth-victorien-ntsana-783a4715b

#### **Profile**

Computer Networking and Cyber Security BSc degree, with over 2 years of experience in Presales network solutions, network support engineer, and extensive customer service experience. Network devices configuration, cisco routers, switches, and ASAs as well as Juniper, FortiGate and Palo Alto firewalls. Now looking for a role as pre-sales solutions consultant or network engineer

## **IT & Key Skills**

- Good knowledge of Computer Network Components and Network Devices configuration
- Good knowledge of Network Protocols including TCP/UDP, ARP, STP, dot1q, DHCP, SMTP, DNS
- Excellent understanding and Working experience with routing protocols such as OSPF, EIGRP, BGP, and redundancy protocols, VRRP/HSRP
- Excellent understanding and working experience with VPLS, MPLS Network, VPN, LANs, VLANs, WLAN. and technologies such as ADSL, FTTC, 4G, Carrier Ethernet and NAT
- Working experience with Cisco, FortiGate, and Palo alto next generation firewalls and next generation UTM firewalls, both centralised and on premise, deployment
- Good Knowledge of firewall UTM features including SSL certificate / full SSL encryption,
   DLP, IPS, Application control, Web filtering/Mail filtering and Anti-virus
- Working experience with voice services, SIP, Hosted Telephony, Voice Connect and UC (Unified Communication)
- Familiar with private and public cloud architecture such as AWS and Microsoft Azure
- Excellent presentation skills and ability to articulate technical concept to a nontechnical audience
- Ability to design a secure, resilient and scalable solutions

### Education

Sept 2015 – June 2018 **BSc (Hons) Computer Networking and Cyber Security**London Metropolitan University

- Topics Include: CCNA R&S, Security in Computing, Network Security (CCNA Security based), Digital Crime Investigation, Ethical Hacking
- Final Year Project: An OSI-Model Approach to Troubleshooting Tools, Methods and Technologies

Oct 2013 – June 2015 HND Network Engineering and Telecommunication System - Merit St- Patrick's college, London

### **Professional Qualifications**

Sept 2016 - CCNA Routing & Switching

April 2019 - CCNP Route (Implementing Cisco IP Routing)
- CCNP Switch (Implementing Cisco IP Switched Network)

Current - CCNA Security

# **Employment Experience**

June 2016 – September 2017 Junior Pre-Sales Solutions Consultant,
EXPONENTIAL-E, Tower Gateway |
June 2018 – Present | Pre-Sales Solution Consultant
EXPONENTIAL-E, Tower Gateway

- Provide solutions design to medium and large organisations or customer's complex network solutions
- Work as a team player to assist in the smooth running of the Pre Sales Solutions department
- Closely interact with the engineering department during the design stage of new solutions
- Working alongside a senior pre-sales solutions consultant and with end customers to complete solutions design and documentations and to respond to tenders
- Arranging conference calls and mettings with existing and new customers to capture customers requirements to be able to provides them with the best possible solution.

January 2018 – June 2018 **Network Support Engineer**, London Metropolitan University, Holloway

- Responding to various network issues including troubleshooting wireless access point.
   Connecting end users to the network, Patching, and configuring cisco routers,
   Switches and Firewalls
- Closely interact with service desk in the process of responding to network problems
- Working alongside Senior network engineer and Senior voice engineer
- Working on a long term project for future development and monitoring the network

**Language:** Native French, Fluent English

**References**, Available On Request